Jodi Tivis

Fort Collins, CO 80525

Phone: 719.355.9114 | Email: joditivis@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jodi-tivis | GitHub: github.com/joditivis |

Portfolio: https://joditivis.github.io/joditivis/

Summary

Front-End Web Developer with a focus and interest in creating a visually rich and aesthetic experience for users. Known as a determined creative, and strong team player, with a willingness to complete whatever task is placed ahead. Excited to be easily adaptable as well as use newly obtained skill sets to best serve any position.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Materialize, JavaScript, jQuery, Firebase, Node JS, MySQL, Express, Sequelize, Handlebars, Mongo DB, Mongoose, and React JS.

Relevant Experience

Portfolio / Business Web Design | Independent

Used web development platforms to create a portfolio for a doctoral graduate
Used web development platforms to create a business website for Full Circle Perspective

Additional Experience

Personal Assistant | Hilary Silver International

Social Media manager/content creator, video editor, event photographer

2018 - Present

Denver, CO

Photographer | Independent

Photographed various events: weddings, maternity, family, business, senior sessions, newborn

2012 - 2020

Clovis, NM, Bentonville, AR, Kailua Kona, HI, Columbus, GA, Denver, CO

Projects

U-Travel | https://github.com/Nicole103/U-Travel

Project Summary: U-Travel is a MERN app that allows users a fun way to plan for vacation. Search flights and hotels, save a packing list, add all trip expenses and keep track of how much they have saved. **Personal Responsibilities:** Using Passport.js I implemented user authentication. I also implemented ReactStrap to create a fun, dynamic, and cohesive UI/UX.

Tools/Languages used: HTML5, CSS3, ReactStrap, React.js, JavaScript, Passport.js, Express, Node JS MongoDB, Mongoose, Weather API, Amadeus API

Restaurant Finder | https://github.com/joditivis/Project2

Project Summary: An 11 question survey takes in a user's location, cravings, dietary restrictions, favorites and more, to help find a restaurant in their area or town they are visiting.

Personal Responsibilities: Web page UI/UX

Tools/Languages used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node JS, Express, Handlebars, MySQL, and

Sequelize ORM

Gif-ting | stacyholtz6.github.io/Gif-ting/ | github.com/joditivis/Gif-ting

Project Summary: Gif-ting allows users to improve on holiday shopping organization and gives users gif(t) ideas for each person they are shopping for.

Personal Responsibilities: Using the GIPHY API, generated a GIF based on each person's word description, as well as a gift generator which generates gift ideas relevant to each person's keyword. **Tools/Languages used:** HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Slick Carousel, Firebase, Etsy API, GIPHY API

Education

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Denver | Denver, CO | September 2019 - March 2020 A six-month intensive web development program focused on gaining technical skills in the most up-to-date developer languages.